realitysandwich.com 2019-10-01

# Privacy Policy | Reality Sandwich

Realitysandwhich.com is a website owned and operated by Delic Corp. and its affiliates (“Delic”, “we” or “us”). Your privacy is very important to us and in order to best protect your information, we have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”), which applies to any and all information you submit to us in connection with your access to and/or use of the Website. It is important to note that this Privacy Policy only applies to information that we collect through Realitysandwich.com and related websites that we own and control (the “Website”). Therefore, if you click any links on the Website that lead to websites owned or operated by third parties or if you access any other website, including to purchase or view any merchandise or material displayed on the Website, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. You should review the privacy policies adopted by those third parties to ensure that you know what information is being collected and for what it is being used. While registration is not required in order to access the Website, certain features and areas of the Website require you to register, create an account and become a member of the Website (each, a “Member” and collectively, “Members”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to your registration for, access to, and/or use of the Website and/or Service. If you do not agree to abide by this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.

By submitting information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy is governed by the Terms of Use, which includes all disclaimers of warranties and limitation of liabilities. All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings set forth in the Terms of Use. A copy of the Terms of Use can be found on the Website.

We may change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time. Whenever we make a material change, we will post or otherwise make available the revised policy. The effective date of the most recent version of this policy will appear at the top of this page.

###  **What Information We Collect and How We Collect It**

Some of the information we collect is Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”). PII, collected only with your consent, may include your first and last name, date of birth, email address, mailing address, phone number and any other information (including MeetDelic registration information) that you provide to us that is linked to your identity. We will only collect PII that is relevant to the services that we provide and the maintenance of the Website. This may occur, for example, in connection with registering to become a Member, subscribing to any of our services, signing up to receive newsletters, responses you provide to survey questions, inquiries you may make through our Website, phone, mail or email, registering a MeetDelic entry and any other information you provide to us. Remember that you always have the option not to provide information by choosing not to use the Website or by not using the particular feature of the Website for which the information is being collected.

We may also collect information through the use of “cookies” or other similar technologies. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your web browser on your hard drive or via mobile IDs. DELIC (and, potentially, third party advertisers or other partners) may set and access cookies on your computer or mobile device to track and store preferential information about you, for purposes such as (i) recognizing you when you return to the Website and use the Service, (ii) tailoring the Website and Service to your specific needs or preferences, and (iii) personalizing the content that you see in order to ensure you enjoy your visit, etc. We may also use Cookies to control the display of ads, to track your Website usage patterns, to record registration and personalization information, and to track the various Website items that you view. DELIC (and potentially third party advertisers) gathers anonymous information about users through Cookie technology on an aggregate level only. Such aggregated information is used within DELIC’s internal organization and is only shared with third party advertisers on an aggregated and non-personally identifiable basis. You can always tell your Internet browser that you don’t want to have any cookies downloaded to your computer. Check with the provider of your particular browser to find out how. Before you do however, note that deleting cookies or directing your browser to refuse them may limit your ability to use certain portions of our Website that require cookies to function. Lastly, third parties who partner with us to display advertising may also use cookies to collect or store data. Please note that your internet browser may enable you to send a message requesting that the Website not track your usage.  As described, we do use this information in order to determine which pages of the Website you view and which links you click in order to tailor our content and advertising for you.  Therefore, the Website currently does not follow these messages from your browser (but again, you may disable Cookies if you so wish).

The last form of information we may collect is non-personally identifying information but relates to your Website or Service usage or is necessary for the proper functioning of the Website or Service, such as the time and date and the extent of your usage of the Website and Service, the location of where you use the Website and Service, your usage preferences, how you interact with other users, which pages of the Website you visit and for how long, the mobile platform or service provider you use, your browser, your operating system, your IP address, and other unique device identifiers (“Other Information”). We may also compile this data to enable statistical analysis of our services that would be used internally or with external assistance to make improvements to our Website. We may also provide this information to third parties, including advertisers. Remember, though, that this information is not personally identifiable. If we ever associate Other Information with you as a specific and identifiable person, we treat it as PII.

Information collected by us may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which we or our agents maintain facilities. By using the Website and Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country, where data protection laws may be different. DELIC makes no representation or warranty with respect to any duty to permanently store any information you may provide. By using the Website or Service and providing us with information, you waive any claims that may arise under your own or any other local or national laws, rules or regulations or international treaties. We may from time to time transfer or merge your information collected off-line to our online databases or store off-line information in an electronic format. We may also combine information we collect online with information available from other sources, including information received from our advertisers and promotional partners. This Privacy Policy applies to your information for as long as your information is in our possession, even if you terminate or discontinue your use of the Website and Service.

###  **Our Use of Information**

We may use the information we collect for a number of purposes. For instance we may use it to enforce the Terms of Use, respond to your inquiries and otherwise correspond with you, to process transactions that you request, to maintain your Member account (if you have one), to customize the content you see on the Website, to maintain the security and integrity of our Website and services, to conduct market research or surveys, and for the administration, review and/or the improvement of the content of our Website and services. We may also use your information to communicate with you about services that we think may interest you or may aggregate your information for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, and detecting and protecting against error or fraud, or as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

You agree that DELIC may use information collected about you to analyse Website usage, improve or customize the Service, customize the Content, respond to your requests, questions and comments, managing your Member account, facilitate communications between users, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy or as DELIC believes necessary to protect its rights and the rights of others, including by enforcing the Terms of Use. You also agree that DELIC may use your information to contact you. Unless you specifically opt out, you agree that DELIC may use your information to deliver information to you that is relevant to your use of the Website or Service such as administrative notices, product enhancements or Service “newsletters”, or that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted advertisements that DELIC believes you may be interested in learning more about. By accepting the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information, unless you specifically opt out in applicable circumstances.

DELIC maintains a strict “no-spam” policy. If you register for the Website and Service, you may receive newsletters, notices and/or special offers via email or text message, unless you have requested otherwise at the time of registration or as set forth below.

You may unsubscribe from these electronic newsletters, notices and/or special offers at any time by following the instructions contained at the very end of every such email or text message or elsewhere as directed by DELIC. If a third party vendor provides such newsletters, you may unsubscribe in accordance with the instructions provided by such third party. If you are having problems unsubscribing please contact us at info@realitysandwich.com (forwarding the newsletter, if applicable, and including in the Subject line the words “Unsubscribe”), and we will use reasonable efforts to remove you within seven (7) business days. Please note that DELIC will not process any unsubscribe requests submitted as direct replies to any newsletter.

###  **Disclosure of Information**

We may share your PII with any unrelated third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or other vendors. We may engage a third party service provider to handle billing for such products or Services on our behalf; provided, that if any third party directly handles payment (such as a mobile service provider, application platform, merchandiser, ticket seller or PayPal), the terms of use and privacy policies of any such third party payment provider will prevail. Further, we may use third parties to outsource one or more aspects of our business (such as email or customer service providers, data processing, and security execution and clearing services), in which case, we would have to disclose to such third parties the PII necessary for such third parties to provide such services.

We also reserve the right, and you hereby authorize us, to share or disclose your PII, including, without limitation, any content, records or electronic communications of any kind, when we determine, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if:

  * you are or may be violating the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy;
  * you are interfering with DELIC’s or a third party’s rights or property;
  * you are violating any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * necessary or required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; and/or
  * requested by governmental authorities in the event of any investigation, act of terrorism or instance of local, regional or national emergency.

In the event that DELIC is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or sells all or substantially all of its assets, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information and content we have received and collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your PII is treated, transferred, or used.

###  **How We Protect Your Information**

DELIC takes a range of security measures designed to protect your information and keep it confidential (unless it is non-confidential by nature, for example, publicly-available information) and free from any unauthorized alteration. However, the internet by its nature is not a secure environment and the nature of security risks is constantly evolving, as are the technical and organizational industry standards relating to management of those risks. While we strive to keep current our security technology and will review, refine and upgrade our security technology as we deem appropriate based on new tools that may become available in the future, the complete security of any information collected, stored or used by us cannot therefore be guaranteed. We have security standards and procedures in place designed to prevent unauthorized access to your Member account and information. A key part of this process helps ensure that all information we have about you is accurate and up-to-date. In the unlikely event that an unauthorized third party compromises DELIC’s security measures, DELIC will not be responsible for any damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party’s ability to view, use or disseminate such information. If you ever discover inaccuracies in our data or if your PII, we urge you to notify us immediately.

You hereby acknowledge that DELIC shall not be responsible or liable for any dissemination of your information that results from your disclosure of such information to any third party.

###  **Links to Third Parties**

The Website may include links to third party websites, apps or services, including payment providers. Such links are not an endorsement by DELIC of those websites, apps and/or the products or services they offer. Third parties have different privacy policies, and DELIC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. If you click on a link to a third party website, app or service, DELIC encourages you to check the applicable privacy policy, as it may differ substantially from that of this Privacy Policy. DELIC makes no representations or warranties nor is DELIC responsible for the privacy policies of any third party. If you decide to access any third party links appearing on the Website, you do so at your own risk.

###  **Children’s Privacy**

The privacy of children is of the utmost importance and we are committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). This Website does not knowingly collect, use, or disclose PII from children under the age of 13. If we ever discover that we have inadvertently collected PII from children under the age of 13, we will delete it as soon as possible. If you are a parent or legal guardian and believe that we have collected PII from your child under the age of 13, please email us at info@realitysandwich.com, and we will take steps to delete this PII as soon as possible.

###  **Access to Your Information**

We will provide you with access to PII you provide us for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. We will also work with you to correct any error in your PII. If you wish to access or correct any PII that you have submitted through our Website, or to have us completely remove your PII from our systems, please send an e-mail with your specific request to info@realitysandwich.com.
